adorika.com 2017-06-06

# Adorika - Privacy policy

Adorika Media (the “Company” or “We”) is committed to protect the privacy of users who access its Website (the “Site”). This Privacy Policy Statement (the “Privacy Policy”) explains the types of information We gather and what We do with it. By using the Site, you agree to the terms and policies described in this Privacy Policy.

1\. Collecting Personally Identifiable Information

“Personally Identifiable Information” means any information obtained through your use of the Site, which might reasonably be used to specifically identify you, and may include, among other, your name, title, company, address and email. To the extent Personally Identifiable Information has been collected from you, you acknowledge such collection is done on a voluntary basis to enable the Company to provide you efficient access to features, functions, promotions, products and services.

In addition, We collect information from you for the purpose of opening an account, collecting billing payment and other payment instruments you use to purchase or order products and services from the Company.

2\. Non-Personal Information

We automatically collect non-personal information such as your IP address during your access and use of the Site to help us diagnose problems with our server, and to identify ways of making our Site better. This information is not linked to any Personally Identifiable Information.

3\. Tracking Technologies, Use and Setting of Digital Identifiers

A 'digital identifier' is a type of information that the Site puts on your hard disk so that it can remember something about you at a later time (Technically speaking, it is information stored by the server on the client side of a client/server communication device for future use, such as “cookies”.) We automatically use ‘digital identifiers’ for tracking transactions, identification, security and user characteristics as set forth herein. No Personally Identifiable Information is collected using digital identifier; We apply the information collected through such digital identifier to analyze trends, administer the Site, track movements on it and gather aggregate demographic information about its visitors, so we can continually improve the Site.

We or our third party advertising partner also employ a software technology called 'clear gifs' (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs) that helps us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information.

4\. Transparency, Choice and Opt-Out

Adorika Media offers consumers the ability to opt-out from our use of data, associated with a Yield Manager cookie, to deliver relevant ads. You can opt-out here <http://content.yieldmanager.edgesuite.net/opt_out.html>. When opting out, Yield Manager will place the opt-out cookie on your computer that will prevent our technology from targeting ads based on your interest. 

If you would like to learn about and edit your ‘digital identifiers’ choices on this Site, please click on “Cookies on this site” located on the homepage to choose the selection appropriate for you. Please note, ‘digital identifiers’ on our site may change periodically; We will update the Site's preference manager accordingly to have the most up to date ‘digital identifiers’ included. 

5\. Security

We employ industry standard security measures to ensure security of all data. Any data that is stored on our servers is treated as proprietary and confidential and is not available to the public. We maintain an internal security policy with respect to the confidentiality of your data, allowing access only to those employees or third parties who have a need to know such information.

While the Company has taken measures to protect your information, please know that (i) no computer system is immune to intrusion; and (ii) information transmitted to the Site may need to pass through many systems in order to be processed. Therefore, We cannot guarantee absolute security or confidentiality of information transmitted to the Site, and you hereby assume and acknowledge the risks related to any kind of such communication. 

_Third Party Links, Social Media Platforms and Third Party ‘Digital Identifiers’._

The Site may offer links to other websites. Other websites have their own terms of use, privacy and security policies. If you choose to visit one of these sites, you should review the policies administered on that particular site.

You acknowledge and confirm that the use of ‘digital identifiers’ by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers is not covered by our privacy statement and is governed by the applicable policies set forth therein. We do not have access or control over those ‘digital identifiers’. Our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers may also use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site, use the shopping cart, etc.

Our Site may also include social media features and scripts, such as the Facebook Like button and widgets or interactive mini-programs that run on the Site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social Media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or directly by our site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the entity providing it.

6\. Permitted Disclosures

Other than as described in this Privacy Policy or as otherwise specifically communicated to you by the Company, the Company does not provide information supplied by users to any third parties, except where law, court order or governmental authority requires; or based upon the good faith belief that disclosure is necessary, including absolute disclosure, to protect the rights of the Company when we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing interference with our rights or harm any third parties.

7\. Revision

Company may alter, update or otherwise modify this Privacy Policy at any time to reflect material changes in the way We use your information. Any such changes will be posted on this page. You should periodically check this Privacy Policy to review the current terms and guidelines applicable to your use of the Site. Your continued use of the Site, after being informed of such changes, will indicate your full acceptance of those changes.

8\. Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please send an e-mail to [sales@adorika.com](mailto:sales@adorika.com). If you believe that we have not complied with this Privacy Policy with respect to your personal information or you have other related inquiries or concerns, you may write to the aforementioned email address.

YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT ANY DISPUTE OVER PRIVACY IS SUBJECT TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AS WELL AS THE GENERAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS BETWEEN YOU, THE COMPANY AND THIS SITE (INCLUDING LIMITATIONS ON DAMAGES).
